IT HELP DESK ANALYST

Summary

Customer Service Representative who maintains a high level of professionalism, patience and efficiency to minimize customer dissatisfaction and increase customer loyalty.

Highlights

- High customer service standards
- Service solutions expert
- Devoted to data integrity
- Strong problem solving ability
- Proficient with Microsoft Office Suite
- Proficient in customer account software
- Conflict resolution proficiency

Accomplishments

Print Graphic Support Â

Collaborated with marketing and business development groups for collateral needs by creating page layout designs for flyers, data sheets,
 CD covers and other printed materials.

Website Design Â

Created accent graphics, banner ads, icons, animations and logos using Photoshop and Illustrator.

Print Design Â

• Designed all graphics and writing content layout for a 250-page cookbook about modern Cambodian cooking.

Collaborated with small team to design and implement enhancements for 14 projects which resulted in a revenue increase of 30%.

Inventory Control

· Restocked and organized items as necessary and as directed.

Documentation

• Reported and documented unsafe conditions, equipment and/or injury.

Preserved an accuracy of [Number]% during [Number] years of employment. Coordinated all department functions for team of [Number]+ employees. Increased office organization by developing more efficient filing system and customer database protocols. Successfully planned and executed corporate meetings, lunches and special events for groups of [Number]+ employees. *Process Improvement* Â

• Oversaw implementation of new phone system which resulted in more cost-effective service.

Research Â

Investigated and analyzed client complaints to identify and resolve issues.

Multitasking Â

• Demonstrated proficiencies in telephone, e-mail, fax and front-desk reception within high-volume environment.

Customer Service Â

 Handled customers effectively by identifying needs, quickly gaining trust, approaching complex situations and resolving problems to maximize efficiency.

Data Preparation Â

Prepared medical records packets for insurance reviews of procedures and fees/services justification.

Administration Â

 Performed administration tasks such as filing, developing spreadsheets, faxing reports, photocopying collateral and scanning documents for inter-departmental use.

Purchasing

Maintained inventory of spare parts inventories and completed purchase requisitions as necessary.

Experience

IT Help Desk Analyst

April 2011 to May 2015 Leidos - The Villages, FL

- Support Global Help Desk call center.
- Correspond by email and phone to interface information back to necessary IT Tier personnel and outside office customers.
- Analyze call incidents in STAT tracking software.
- Enter ORACLE, Portal, and E-mail security passwords for North, South America, and Canada offices.
- Collect and Review Internal Auditors requests submitted for new employee access to domestic location servers; regarding Sarbanes Oxley documentation.
- Initiate corporate employee terminations assigned thru Human Resource Departments for final processing and removal of all open data access.
- Coordinate with purchasing manager on price quotes for hardware and software.
- Inventory stock network fiber wire, patch cables, splitters, memory, mice and keyboards.
- Prepare replacement wireless devices deleting stored data; determine device condition for return and recycling with corresponding carriers.
- Collect personal ID's, Serial & Model Numbers for tracking purposes.
- Developed and maintain Human Resource personnel Images for Security Badges, ADUC and Email.
- Process Legal Department imaging in regards to various confidential records.

Web Multimedia Designer

May 2002 to April 2011 Matthews International - Stone Mountain, GA

- Oversaw the maintenance, updates and redesigns of existing websites review, analyze and understand the business's needs customer base, then design and implement the necessary improvements for the corporate sites.
- Working with the IT department, programmers, graphic designers, marketing and sales directors, was responsible the flow of service and
 maintenance of the company site, as well as the implementation of regular updates such as banners, promotional information, images and
 resources.
- Editing of HTML and CSS style sheets, for design, and creation of graphic elements used.
- Set up and maintained online replacement parts and accessories sales store for customer service division with C.C.
- acceptance incorporated.
- Front end integration of OXO Oracle i-Store programming environment working with backend staff on Shipping, Warehouse Supply, Purchasing, Email, Questionnaires and Forms.
- Testing and analyzing for breaks in sites development content and all active connections.

Computer Graphics Artist

May 1989 to May 2002 Helen Of Troy L.P - City, STATE

- Production Artist in charge of design, layout, mock-up and packaging concepts for the complete lines of Revlon, Vidal Sassoon, Lady Dazey, Dr.
- Scholl's and Carel/Carruso personal care products.
- Developed and instituted a complete digital archiving system for over 800 products and related documents.
- Designed national selling brush and accessory lines that generated over 20 million in profits.
- Attended press checks and also arranged and directed photography sessions.

Production Artist

January 1986 to May 1989 SWGM Advertising - City, STATE

- Created and handled production work through improved planning, scheduling, and training.
- Consistently attained shorter work around times on all brochures, presentations, catalogs and signage.
- For such clients as Savanne, Billy the Kid, Sanders Boots, Farah Manufacturing and Sheldon's Jewelry companies.
- Specializing in men's clothing in-store presentation and sales ticketing.

Education

Day Boot Camp Oracle University I-Store Web Development and Implementation Certification #2412557: I-Store Development Oracle University - City, State, usa

3 Day Boot Camp for Web Store Development and Implementation

B&W: Photography and Development, 8/28/1989 Western Technical Institute Photography and Development

Certification: 1/1980 University of Texas El Paso

Cultural Art & History, 9/15/1979 International Collage of London Cultural Art & History

Graduate: 1979 Eastwood High School

Skills

Artist, banners, brochures, C, cables, call center, catalogs, hardware, content, CSS, clients, customer service, documentation, Editing, E-mail, Email, Forms, graphic, Help Desk, HTML, Human Resource, imaging, Inventory, layout, Legal, marketing and sales, memory, access, office, network, Oracle i, ORACLE, packaging, personnel, photography, presentations, press, programming, Purchasing, selling, sales, Sarbanes Oxley, scheduling, servers, Shipping, style sheets, phone, Web Development, websites